import { Game } from "../types/game_types";

export const Games: Game[] = [
    {
        id: 1,
        title: "(Testing) Game 1",
        description: "Description 1",
        settings: {
            answerTimeout: 15
        },
        questions: [
            {
                questionText: "Question 1",
                videoYouTubeID: "dQw4w9WgXcQ",
                videoStartTime: 15,
                videoEndTime: 30,
                answer: "Answer 1",
                answerSubtext: "Answer 1 Subtext"
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 2",
                videoYouTubeID: "dQw4w9WgXcQ",
                videoStartTime: 30,
                videoEndTime: 45,
                answer: "Answer 2",
                answerSubtext: "Answer 2 Subtext"
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 3",
                videoYouTubeID: "dQw4w9WgXcQ",
                videoStartTime: 45,
                videoEndTime: 60,
                answer: "Answer 3",
                answerSubtext: "Answer 3 Subtext"
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        title: "(Testing) Holiday Mix",
        description: "Festive songs for the festive season!",
        settings: {
            answerTimeout: 15
        },
        questions: [
            {
                questionText: "Question 1",
                videoYouTubeID: "9DlD7-TykIU",
                videoStartTime: 20,
                videoEndTime: 35,
                answer: "O Holy Night",
                answerSubtext: "A festive classic"
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 2",
                videoYouTubeID: "9DlD7-TykIU",
                videoStartTime: 225,
                videoEndTime: 240,
                answer: "Silent Night",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 3",
                videoYouTubeID: "9DlD7-TykIU",
                videoStartTime: 370,
                videoEndTime: 385,
                answer: "Angels We Have Heard on High",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 4",
                videoYouTubeID: "9DlD7-TykIU",
                videoStartTime: 535,
                videoEndTime: 550,
                answer: "O Come All Ye Faithful",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 5",
                videoYouTubeID: "2bvNZvGX7C0",
                videoStartTime: 15,
                videoEndTime: 30,
                answer: "We Wish You a Merry Christmas",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 6",
                videoYouTubeID: "2bvNZvGX7C0",
                videoStartTime: 380,
                videoEndTime: 395,
                answer: "Deck the Halls",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 7",
                videoYouTubeID: "G1Eq0f5mMVQ",
                videoStartTime: 70,
                videoEndTime: 85,
                answer: "First Noel",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 8",
                videoYouTubeID: "G1Eq0f5mMVQ",
                videoStartTime: 590,
                videoEndTime: 605,
                answer: "Away in the Manger",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 9",
                videoYouTubeID: "G1Eq0f5mMVQ",
                videoStartTime: 1150,
                videoEndTime: 1175,
                answer: "Greensleeves",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 10",
                videoYouTubeID: "G1Eq0f5mMVQ",
                videoStartTime: 1890,
                videoEndTime: 1905,
                answer: "Joy to the World",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
        ],
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        title: "Christmas",
        description: "Group 1 of festive songs",
        settings: {
            answerTimeout: 15
        },
        questions: [
            {
                questionText: "Question 1",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 316,
                videoEndTime: 347,
                answer: "Oh Christmas Tree",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 2",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 348,
                videoEndTime: 374,
                answer: "We Wish You a Merry Christmas",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 3",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 376,
                videoEndTime: 399,
                answer: "God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 4",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 400,
                videoEndTime: 420,
                answer: "Deck the Halls",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 5",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 422,
                videoEndTime: 442,
                answer: "Joy to the World",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 6",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 268,
                videoEndTime: 288,
                answer: "Mele KalikiMaka",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        title: "Christmas: The Sequel",
        description: "Group 2 of festive songs",
        settings: {
            answerTimeout: 15
        },
        questions: [
            {
                questionText: "Question 1",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 444,
                videoEndTime: 468,
                answer: "Go Telling on the Mountain",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 2",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 472,
                videoEndTime: 493,
                answer: "O Holy Night",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 3",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 496,
                videoEndTime: 511,
                answer: "Jingle Bells",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 4",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 515,
                videoEndTime: 537,
                answer: "Hark! The Herald Angels Sing",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 5",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 900,
                videoEndTime: 908,
                answer: "It's Beginning to Look a Lot Like Christmas",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 6",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 288,
                videoEndTime: 316,
                answer: "Carol of the Bells",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        title: "Games",
        description: "Answer in the form of a game",
        settings: {
            answerTimeout: 15
        },
        questions: [
            {
                questionText: "Question 1",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 651,
                videoEndTime: 667,
                answer: "Skyrim",
                answerSubtext: "You're finally awake"
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 2",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 670,
                videoEndTime: 703,
                answer: "Tetris",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 3",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 704,
                videoEndTime: 749,
                answer: "Papers Please",
                answerSubtext: "Golory to Arstotzka"
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 4",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 750,
                videoEndTime: 780,
                answer: "Undertale",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 5",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 781,
                videoEndTime: 797,
                answer: "Dota",
                answerSubtext: "Hunting that Bass"
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 6",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 798,
                videoEndTime: 817,
                answer: "Crash Bandicoot",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 7",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 819,
                videoEndTime: 842,
                answer: "Fortnite",
                answerSubtext: "Just wiped out Tomato Town"
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        title: "Miscellaneous",
        description: "Stuff that didn't fit anywhere else",
        settings: {
            answerTimeout: 15
        },
        questions: [
            {
                questionText: "Question 1",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 15,
                videoEndTime: 23,
                answer: "Viva La Vida",
                answerSubtext: "Coldplay"
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 2",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 576,
                videoEndTime: 609,
                answer: "Natural",
                answerSubtext: "Imagine Dragons"
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 3",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 24,
                videoEndTime: 75,
                answer: "Umbrella",
                answerSubtext: "Rihanna"
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 4",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 123,
                videoEndTime: 156,
                answer: "Fly Me to the Moon",
                answerSubtext: "Frank Sinatra"
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 5",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 157,
                videoEndTime: 198,
                answer: "Gravity Falls Theme",
                answerSubtext: ""
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 6",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 611,
                videoEndTime: 650,
                answer: "Enemy",
                answerSubtext: "Imagine Dragons"
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        title: "Cursed",
        description: "Songs that are obscure and/or turned out comicly bad",
        settings: {
            answerTimeout: 15
        },
        questions: [
            {
                questionText: "Question 1",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 0,
                videoEndTime: 13,
                answer: "Hall of the Mountain King",
                answerSubtext: "Some dead guy idk"
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 2",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 844,
                videoEndTime: 897,
                answer: "Money Money Money",
                answerSubtext: "ABBA"
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 3",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 78,
                videoEndTime: 120,
                answer: "Fireflies",
                answerSubtext: "Owl City"
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 4",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 200,
                videoEndTime: 233,
                answer: "Sincerely Me",
                answerSubtext: "Dear Even Hansen"
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 5",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 541,
                videoEndTime: 574,
                answer: "Merry-Go-Round of Life",
                answerSubtext: "Howl's Moving Castle"
            },
            {
                questionText: "Question 6",
                videoYouTubeID: "qZmErriuvnU",
                videoStartTime: 235,
                videoEndTime: 266,
                answer: "Gotta Get Back to Hogwarts",
                answerSubtext: "A Very Potter Musical"
            },
        ]
    }
]